Hannah "Hallie" Dudley Columbia, South Carolina

HDUDLEY@email.sc.edu | US Mobile: +1 (980) 253 1711 | LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/hallie-dudley-02a2a0283

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

MSBA candidate with undergraduate degree in Mathematics and Computer Science. Interested in **Data Science** and **Data Analytics**, within the **Healthcare** or **Business** industry. Proven ability to understand high level math. Experienced in computer programming and data visualization. Natural ability to pivot between a keen understanding of both quantitative and qualitative aspects and interact comfortably and effectively in teams and individually.

EDUCATION

MOORE SCHOOL OF BUSINESS, University of South Carolina

Columbia, SC USA

Master of Science in Business Analytics (MSBA). Current GPA 4.0/4.0

August 2023 - present

Honors: Outstanding Overall MSBA Student Award, Perfect GPA certificate.

Courses: Big Data Analytics, Data Resource Management, Data Science for Business Decision Making, Project Management, Quantitative Methods in Business, Advanced Quantitative Methods in Business.

WOFFORD COLLEGE Spartanburg, SC USA

Bachelor of Arts, Mathematics. Minor Computer Science. Phi Beta Kappa. Summa cum Laude. GPA 3.98 / 4.0 August

2019 - May 2023

Benjamin Wofford Scholarship, Wofford Scholars program, Dean's List (all semesters), Wofford Ambassador.

Courses: Calculus 1 & 2, Multivariable Calculus, Differential Equations, Partial Differential Equations, Linear Algebra, Mathematical Proofs, Statistical Modeling, Chaos Theory, Programming & Problem Solving, Data Structures & Algorithms, Programming Languages, Data Science.

WORK EXPERIENCE

LILBELLE - women's clothing boutique

Retail Sales Associate (June 2021 – August 2022)

Charlotte, NC USA

June 2021 – August 2022

Greeted Customers and answered product questions. Performed general store upkeep as per site standards, such as cleaning and organizing floor inventory. Maintained floor inventory displays and updated customer records.

• Reorganized house inventory to ease backstock. Used space provided and created a system to categorize inventory and label product locations, expediting fast item retrieval that eliminated wait time for customers or for general floor stocking demands.

Market Trend Analyst Intern (June 2022 – August 2022)

Created new ideas that optimized efficiency while also working as a retail associate. Served as store lead in owner absence.

- Observed patterns in customer shopping habits to recommend items suitable to customers' preferences and requests.
- Worked with shop owner to learn about successful new inventory items and assisted in new stock selections.
- Using prior experience and customer feedback, reorganized the sales floor aesthetics and improved the store layout navigation.

CRAFTING SCHOLARS - customized tutoring company for general academics and standardized testing

Charlotte, NC USA

Math Associate

May 2021 - July 2021

Learned strategies to tutor children in unique ways in general Math and SAT/ACT Math. Reviewed SAT/ACT practice exams to determine individual improvement plans. Performed general office duties at a site of 8 employees.

- Researched and collected US college counselor data to grow the business/client base.
- Created a detailed Excel spreadsheet including all counselor contact details for office reference.

IT - ANALYTICAL

General Applications Excel, Word, PowerPoint, Outlook

Data Analysis R, regression, Power BI, Power Query

Database-Programming C++, Python; basic knowledge in SQL, Erlang, Racket

Marketing-Design basic point-of-sale retail, basic photoshop

LEADERSHIP EXPERIENCE

President, Zeta Tau Alpha Fraternity, Wofford College, (2021 – 2022) Served as Wofford College representative to National Organization. Led Executive Council (13 members) and Chapter meetings for 130 members weekly. Responsible for all aspects of the organization from contracts and national orders to safety and membership.

Treasurer, Zeta Tau Alpha Fraternity, Wofford College, (2020 – 2021) Handled financials for all 130 members, created and mana annual budget, and oversaw all payments to National Organization, as well as external vendors for various events.	aged